this is the generation that changes
everything
not the Millennials or Gen X or the
Boomers but everybody who's alive today
has a role to play in creating a new
society a society that works for
absolutely everyone unleashes their true
potential we're gonna unleash humanity's
potential we used to think we only used
what was it ten percent of the brain we
are only using one percent of humanity
and even those people the people who are
looked at as leaders who have access to
more intelligence or more goodness or
more power they can't access all of who
they are if the rest of humanity isn't
joining them just like a nomad as an
island you can't actually be a self
success because you need roads
you need doctors need engineers no one
person can do it so the more we create
the tools it allows absolutely everyone
to give their piece in a way that is
self fulfilling that fulfills you from
the inside out doesn't mean we're not
necessarily gonna find a form of payment
it definitely doesn't mean we're not
gonna have resources everyone will have
all of the resources they need because
when you unlock humanity there's more
than enough people to create the
resources
to create the systems the ways of
knowing and being we get to be alive and
the best of times in the worst of times
and it only takes a handful of us to
start
I've already started I'm already
showcasing my journey and other people
all around me and all around the world
are following their own path their own
journey towards their purpose their
vision we don't need one vision we don't
need one religion we don't need one way
to make sense of the world there are
tools we need to create so that we
collectively can make sense of the
things we've been trying to make sense
of since the dawn of time our bodies in
health science history economics maybe
not since the beginning of time but
since we created barter and currency
political systems since we stopped being
small tribes that everyone knew everyone
once we had kings the political system
and this system this new way of being
this new society is going to prove it to
starting people and as they move forward
it's gonna prove itself as we go every
step of the way
that doesn't mean we're gonna do
everything perfectly we're gonna get it
perfectly wrong we're gonna get exactly
the right lessons we're meant to learn
and I know what that sounds like and I
no longer care because it's the truth
and you can be skeptical as long as
there's curiosity there too
and that curiosity will allow skepticism
to eventually subside because it'll
prove itself to you I am a very
skeptical person I was a very skeptical
person so my signs had to be big I had
to figure out how we saved the entire
planet our entire species how to unlock
humanity in order to feel worthy in
order to see that everybody is worthy
and I have always been worthy and
whether or not this thing inside of me
is the future we live in - it's not it's
the combination of all of our futures
our generation gets to create a better
world and the next generation our
children's children's children this is
different this is a different time
period because it isn't going to be
Thomas Edison or even Elon Musk and Jeff
Bezos
it's gonna be all of us it's going to be
tens it's gonna be handful and then it's
gonna be hundreds and then it's gonna be
thousands and then it's gonna be
millions and then it's gonna be billions
it's not a light switch
we don't just flip it and everyone's
enlightened everyone's a genius it's
each person who feels called starting on
the path proving it to themselves and
then finding other people
and together starting projects and doing
activities that change their lives and
the lives of other people and then more
people start because they have the
capacity to this isn't get rich and
handout the charity but it is step
forward and look back to those you can
help forward
a better world is on its way and we all
get a participate in creating it
together please like and subscribe and
hit that little bell there's gonna be a
lot happening in the next few weeks